Today, we are going to be discussing humiliation.
Definition: Humiliation is the abasement of pride, which creates mortification
or leads to a state of being humbled or reduced to submission.
It's an emotion felt by a person whose status, either forced or willingly, has just
decreased. It can be brought about through intimidation, physical or mental trickery,
or by embarrassment. Erotic humiliation is consensual
psychological humiliation performed in order to produce erotic excitement or sexual
arousal. This can either be for the person being humiliated, or the person humiliating,
or both. The specifics. Here are some examples.
You can either pause the video here and take pictures, screenshots, or write it down
in a notepad. Here
are some more examples. And
some more. And
finally. We
really hope these humiliation tactics help you when you're on cam.
As you can see, there is a lot there, and there is a long list to choose from.
So we would recommend printing them off and having them next to you, or if not, you
can write them all down in a little notepad and keep it with you at all times when
you're camming. That way, if a humiliation client enters your room, you have a really
long list of things to do with them and try with them.
With that being said, I would recommend just taking a slow, especially with new clients.
Don't give them something that's too humiliating to begin with.
Just give them a more easier one to perform and see how they get on and then up it,
you know, up it more and more and more of how humiliating it is.
You don't want to go straight in with a really bad one and then it might scare them
off. So just gauge it with each client and see what they're comfortable with.
Like I said, you don't want to do something that's too much and then you'll scare
them off. And that could be a potential really long client that you make a lot of
money from. So, yeah, good luck, girls. And I'm excited to see all your journeys
and see how you're all getting on. See ya.